The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The first Suzaku sacrificed himself
along with 9 Middle stage Ascendant cultivators
to make the 5 Sealing Swords
and seal the Forsaken Immortal Clan for tens of thousands of years.
But today,
Original Ancestor of the
Forsaken Immortal Clan
11-Leaf
this old man can rival peak Ascendant !
No one can stop my clan from taking back planet Fu Wen !
Back then,
this old man was but a coward
who had to watch countless clan members die.
For tens of thousands of years,
they fed me the lives of my own brethren
because I was the Ancestor.
This old man is a sinner...
I deserve to die...
I will be sealed by these swords
in place of the Forsaken Immortal Tree.
I offer my soul
as sacrifice.
In exchange,
the Forsaken Immortal Clan
will be free !
I will die for the Dao
so that my clan
may walk this earth again !
Ancestral Spirit Tree
Forsaken Immortal Clan
Forsaken Immortal Clan,
bid farewell to the Ancestor.
Farewell Ancestor.
Take back the planet !
Kill !
As the 14th generation Suzaku,
I command all countries of planet Suzaku
to wage war against
the Forsaken Immortal Clan !
Even if I'm one step from Soul Transformation,
the amount of celestial jades I have
is far from enough to breakthrough.
Celestial jades are rare.
I must return to the Soul Refining Sect first
to seek Senior Du Tian’s guidance.
This is…
the Forsaken Immortal Clan ?
Country of Zhao
Wang Zhuo
Xuan Dao Sect Elder
Late stage Core Formation
Be careful !
Junior Brother !
You Forsaken Immortal bandits,
come out and face me !
That’s…
Pang Long
Forsaken Immortal Clan
6-Leaf Shaman
a 6-leaf Shaman !
Little brats
you can keep trying,
I'm not done playing with you.
Since you refuse to surrender,
I let my Juniors will practice on you !
I’ll fight you to the death !
Boring.
Die !
Break.
Who’s there ?!
Soul Transformation !
Run !
Mosquito Beast !
When you reach Nascent Soul,
you will remember the past.
It’s you ?
The Senior that reached Soul Formation at Heng Yue...
A few years have passed
and you’re already at Late stage Core Formation.
Not bad.
Unfortunately, I haven't managed to form a Nascent Soul.
I’ll help you.
Wang Zhuo
Xuan Dao Sect Elder
Early stage Nascent Soul
Wang Lin...
Thank you.
We're the last remnants of the Wang Family,
you don't need to thank me.
Times have changed...
We once took the Spirit Root test together.
Who could’ve imagined
that things would turn out like this ?
What happened
for planet Suzaku to be in this state ?
You don’t know !?
These past few years,
I haven’t been on planet Suzaku.
Wang Lin’s cultivation
can now traverse the void...
3 years ago,
the Forsaken Immortal Clan declared war against Suzaku.
The country of Suzaku called all countries for help in the war.
But who would've thought
that the Forsaken Immortal Clan plotted for millennia.
They had sent 9 cultivators to the surface
to infiltrate important countries.
Now, these 9 all hold key positions.
Only 5 of them have been exposed.
But with their help from within,
the country of Suzaku was forced to retreat.
To try to turn the tide,
Qian Feng challenged the Forsaken Immortal Clan's young patriarch alone.
After 3 days and 3 nights,
Their duel
ended in a draw.
After the stalemate,
the Forsaken Immortal Clan agreed to a truce.
But no one expected
that the condition for this truce
was for Suzaku to cede all countries under rank 4
and hand over their cultivators and gifted children.
Since then
all rank 3 countries have been in this state.
Some were forced to surrender
and others refused to yield,
becoming a living hell.
Our Country of Zhao is struggling to hold on.
We're at our wit's end.
The mission of our squad
was to get help from a rank 4 country
in hope that someone will accept to shelter us.
But...
not only did they coldly refuse
but they even mocked us for resisting.
And problems never come alone,
we were ambushed by the Forsaken Immortal Clan on our way back.
I fear it won't be long
before Zhao falls too.
Wang Lin,
can you return to Zhao ?
Master,
if this Senior is so powerful,
couldn't he resolve our country's crisis ?
If he helps us,
he'd make enemies of both sides.
In these times,
no one wants be in this kind of situation.
Your Highness
3 children in the capital
were already taken by the outsiders.
Wang Qi
Prince of Zhao
Queen consort of Zhao
Wang Yu
Crown prince of Zhao
Are you sure that place can protect Yu'er ?
I'm not sure.
But my great-grandfather told me
the family's oldest rule:
When facing annihilation,
enter the Ancestral Home
and your life will be saved.
What's so special about that Ancestral Home ?
Before our Wang Family came to the capital,
one of us became a powerful Immortal.
He's known as the Ancestor.
The Ancestral Home
must contain something he left.
But after all these years,
I'm not sure if it's true.
Where have all the Immortals from the capital gone ?
They could've protected us !
They returned to their sects to fight.
If defeated,
they'll gather at a designated place.
The Sect Formation is falling !
Wufeng Valley
Everyone, retreat to Heng Yue Mountain !
Hurry !
Did you tell everyone ?
They all went to Heng Yue Mountain.
Let's go !
Quick, into the Ancestral Home !
You run quite fast
Your Highness...
Hand over this children with a Spirit Root
and I'll spare your lives.
Never !
Your country is interesting,
why did you gather here like this ?
Does this place
hide some artifacts ?
You're welcome to try.
Interesting !
Let me see
what makes you so confident.
The Ancestor !
He really exists...
This is the legacy of the Ancestor of Zhao,
it will surely protect us !
The Ancestor has appeared !
I knew he would protect us !
It's actually a domain artifact...
Greetings, Elder !
But its owner's cultivation is too weak.
Mo Luo
Forsaken Immortal Clan
6-Leaf Shaman
Merely Early stage Soul Formation...
Even if he came here personally,
he wouldn't survive,
let alone his artifact.
The country's artifact is attacked !
what do we do ?
This object is intriguing.
It would be a pity to destroy it.
It's a real treasure !
For this object's sake,
I won't make things difficult for you.
Become vassals of our Forsaken Immortal Clan
and you'll far better than under Suzaku.
What do you think ?
Dream on !
We'll defend Zhao to the death !
We'll never surrender !
In that case,
the Country of Zhao
shall be destroyed today !
You
are unworthy.
Ancestor !
His cultivation is unfathomable.
At first glance, Peak Late stage Soul Formation
but it contains a strange power...
Hand over
the wood carving.
Tattoo,
explode !
What !?
He neutralized my attack so easily ?
It's just a rank 3 country's Ancestor
but he's a Soul Transformation old monster !
Why is this happening to me ?
Did I allow you to leave ?
Sir,
we have a truce with Suzaku.
Do you dare to break it ?
So what if I do ?
Since it has come to this,
I must use the Reincarnation Tree's power to go back !
Stop !
If you kill me,
there will be a lingering tattoo curse on you.
When my Seniors see it
they will kill you.
I have already killed quite a few
Forsaken Immortal Clan members.
6-leaf Warrior ?
And even Shamans !
No...
Impossible !
Absorb !
Junior Zhen Fengxiao of the Xuan Dao Sect
pays respects to Ancestor.
I'm not your Ancestor.
Note: they say 200 but it's incorrect
100 years ago,
when you reached Soul Formation at the Xuan Dao Sect,
you earned the title of Ancestor.
And now,
you've saved Zhao
from certain destruction.
Fulfilling the Ancestor's role.
You are Zhao rightful Ancestor !
My son,
it doesn't matter if you aren't chosen.
You can always come back home,
you still have your parents.
500 years have passed...
We pay Respects to Zhao's Ancestor !
Lectures on cultivation
to clarify the right path
will help Core Formations form Nascent Souls.
Seeing a domain
and understanding the heavens
gives Nascent Souls hope for Soul Formation.
Stronger formations
will help resist invaders.
Only a Soul Transformation can break them.
The future of Zhao
will depend on their own fate.
Have you decided ?
In both my lives,
the Wang Family raised me.
All I want now
is to spend my remaining time
protecting future generations !
Matters of the past
end here.
I too must attend to my duties.
Take care.
Little friend Ceng Niu,
you're finally back.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.